

# Gheorghe Madalina-Eleonora

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

**Bucharest** 

Romania

0768792728

madalinaeleonora.gheorghe@gmail.com

#### Links

Personal Website

Linkedin

GitHub

Medium

#### Skills

JavaScript

Angular

React

Vue

TypeScript

Effective Time Management

Analytical Thinking

Team player

# Languages

English

Romanian

# **Hobbies**

Technology, Photography, Cars

#### **Profile**

I am an experienced Front-end Developer who works in a proactive way, every time ready to face challenges and working well under pressure. I am creative and my analytical thinking is helping me to find solutions for difficult situations.

# **Employment History**

Consultant / Frontend Developer, Deloitte Digital, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

Overall technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, Angular, React, Thymeleaf, Mambu, TypeScript, AWS Services, Java

- Client 2: Germany (02/2022 Present) Banking
- Client 1: Alpha Team United Kingdom (10/2021 01/2022) Banking, Insurance

See details on website.

#### Frontend Developer, IBM Romania, Bucharest

DECEMBER 2018 - OCTOBER 2021

Overall technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, REST, Sass, Angular, VirtualBox, Ionic, TypeScript, Capacitor, RxJs, React.js, Adobe Experience Manager

- Client 3: United States (04/2020 10/2021) E-Commerce
- Client 2: United Kingdom (03/2020 03/2020) Retail
- Client 1: Germany (03/2019 03/2020) Reinsurance
- Internship: Germany (12/2018 02/2019) Reinsurance

See details on website.

Practicant - Drive your future, Groupe Renault, Bucharest

JUNE 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Database maintenance using my own Matlab scripts, SQL Database and C#.

#### Education

Master's degree in Information Technology Administration and Management, Romanian-American University, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2018 - JULY 2020

Bachelor degree in Information Technology Administration and Management, Romanian-American University, Bucharest

OCTOBER 2015 - JULY 2018

# **Awards**

2nd place at Rau-DevHack Hackathon

APRIL 2019

1st place for Web&Mobile Challenge at DevHacks

NOVEMBER 2018

# Certifications

Angular (Intermediate) - HackerRank

MARCH 2022

Link to certificate

#### IBM Mentor - IBM Romania

DECEMBER 2020

#### Link to badge

#### JavaScript Front End Development - IBM Romania

DECEMBER 2020

Link to badge

### IBM Agile Explorer - IBM Romania

MARCH 2020

Link to badge

# **Projects**

#### Master's Degree Project, Bucharest

SEPTEMBER 2019 - JULY 2020

Search for your best option through hundred of updated universities around the world. Users can grade and add a comment to institutions so others can see if it fits for them. Only verified ratings will be displayed.

#### See code and live

### **Bachelor's Degree Project, Bucharest**

MARCH 2018 - JUNE 2019

Tracking weather and traffic conditions, using AccuWeather, Google Maps and Google Charts APIs for your next trip.

#### See code and live

#### Hackathons projects, Bucharest

- Hipo DevHack Nov 2020 See live and code
- RAU DevHack Apr 2019 See live and code
- Microsoft Do IT Girls Mar 2019 See live and code
- Hipo DevHack Nov 2018 See live and code

### Other personal projects

MARCH 2018 - PRESENT

Other personal projects are available on my Website or GitHub Profile

# Latest recommendations

#### Silvana-Roberta Helal, Senior Manager in Deloitte Digital

MAY 2022

"Madalina recently joined our team and rapidly adapted to the project specifics and pace. Feedback from both team and local technical lead is positive as Madalina started working on the project near stabilization phase, but managed to get familiar in a short timeframe with the complexity of the project [...]" See more on website.

# Diego Frison Aladren, Solution Lead in Deloitte Digital

APRIL 2022

"Madalina joined the team in a very critical moment [...] She could quickly take over the tasks assigned to her and she could deliver them with a very good quality on the agreed time. Madalina is also a team player and she knows when she need to raise the hand [...]" See more on website.

### Other recommendations

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

See more on website.